JOAQUIM GIFRE ROSALES

Arenys de Mar (Barcelona) · 666442891 jgifrerosales@gmail.com · www.linkedin.com/in/joaquim-gifre-rosales

As a Full-stack developer I have worked on different projects focused on different areas, such as eHealth, Big Data or Security, in conjunction with various multidisciplinary teams, using the most recent technologies and methodologies to reach the best solution. Teamwork is important as you may be helping or learning something new from a coworker. I consider mandatory the use of methodologies and testing tools for the healthy evolution of the projects.

WORK HISTORY

2018-02 - PRESENT

SOFTWARE ENGINEER, EURECAT

Full-Stack role: design, development and deployment of web-based application using recent technologies and Agile methodologies depending on client requirements.

- Designing and developing complex systems.
- Building the project architecture and using Docker to deploy different services based on Python, Java, Nginx and Tomcat.
- Work in cooperation with other departments and clients to design and develop different web-apps.

2017-05 - 2018-02

SOFTWARE ENGINEER (INTERNSHIP), EURECAT

Helping coworkers while learning Full-Stack developer role.

EDUCATION

2022

ASSOCIATE CERTIFICATION AS UNITY PROGRAMMER, UNITY TECHNOLOGIES 2020 - 2022

MASTERS DEGREE IN VIDEOGAME DESIGN AND DEVELOPMENT, UNIVERSITAT OBERTA DE CATALUNYA (UOC)

2012 - 2018

DEGREE IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING, UNIVERSITAT DE BARCELONA (UB)

SKILLS

- Backend (Spring, SpringBoot, Hibernate, Mockito, Junit5, SQL Databases, MongoDB).
- Frontend (Angularjs, Angular, CSS, HTML, TypeScript, JavaScript).
- DevOps and Other tools (Docker, Nginx, Tomcat, Postman, git, Script, Jenkins, SonarQube).
- Game Engines (Unity (C#))